RAHUL NS ANAND

Bengaluru, IN 560100 - (869) 006-1328 – rahulanand2206@gmail.com linkedin.com/in/rahulnsanand github.com/rahulnsanand

Professional Software Engineer with 4 years experience in designing, developing and deploying production grade .net Core MVC and Full Stack Java applications. Seeking to use proven skills in Application Development and Technical Leadership to make. Key skills include:

Quick Learner - Java - .NET Core - React - Scripting

Analytical Thinking - Docker - Linux - Android Development - Power BI

WORK EXPERIENCE

Software Development Engineer 1 – Deloitte USI, Bengaluru

06/2023 - present

- o <u>Tailor your experience</u> sections to the job description. Don't use up too much of your space detailing daily duties that aren't relevant to the job for which you're applying.
- Study the job listing to figure out what's most important to the hiring manager.
- Use important <u>resume keywords</u> and accomplishments that speak to your ability to execute.

Software Development Associate – Deloitte USI, Bengaluru

06/2021 - 06/2022

- Work the hard skills and keywords found in the job description right into your resume. That said, simply listing the keywords in these dedicated skills sections is not enough.
- Recruiters want to see context that proves that you actually possess the skill.
- For example, if you mention a piece of software like Microsoft Excel, Adobe Photoshop, or AutoCAD, mention the types of projects it was used for.

Software Analyst - Deloitte USI, Bengaluru

12/2020 - 06/2021

- Recruiters like to be able to get an idea of why you move from company to company. Demonstrate your increasing impact and responsibility from job to job.
- This shows the recruiter that you're capable of taking on more and more and gives them an idea of where your career is heading.

PROJECTS

BurgerLife – Privatized Cloud Solutions

 Recruiters like to be able to get an idea of why you move from company to company. Demonstrate your increasing impact and responsibility from job to job.

TickTrack – Published Android Application

- Recruiters like to be able to get an idea of why you move from company to company. Demonstrate your increasing impact and responsibility from job to job.
- This shows the recruiter that you're capable of taking on more and more and gives them an idea of where your career is heading.

EDUCATION

B.Tech Computer Science Engineering – SRM Institute of Science and Technology, Chennai

Year - 2020

HOBBIES

Gaming - Badminton - Trekking - Digital Content Creation - Problem Solving